

## **CONTACT**



(**៤))** +34 634 657 688



maolin1698@gmail.com



Sevilla, Spain



https://www.linkedin.com/in/m ao-lin-193064221/



## **DIGITAL SKILLS**

### **Programming**

- Python
- Java
- C
- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- React.js
- Flask
- Django
- Robot Framework
- Selenium
- VHDL

### Infrastructure as code

- Git
- SVN
- Jenkins
- Docker

### **Others**

- JIRA
- MATLAB
- JAMA
- MS Office
- SpiraTest
- Wireshark

### **OTHER SKILLS**

- · Agile methodologies such as scrums, sprints, etc.
- Proactive.
- Flexible.
- · Solution-oriented.
- · Good communication.

# **MAO LIN**

Telecommunication engineer specialized in the field of electronics with near 5 year of experience in automated testing environments with CI/CD.

My ultimate passion is combining software and hardware and make it work in our day to day life.



## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

### **QA TEST ENGINEER**

Woodswallow, Spain (Jan. 2022 - Nov. 2024)

- · Requirements traceability matrix analysis and coverage.
- · Test cases design, implementation and result analysis with Robot Framework.
- Development of Jenkins and GitLab environment for CI/CD pipelines
- Python back-end development of internal framework automated for testing.
- · Testing and handling of DLMS, IDIS, PRIME and ZigBee compliant devices.

### **QA TEST ENGINEER**

AICIA, Spain (Jun. 2020 - Jan. 2022)

- · Test cases design, implementation and result analysis.
- Back-end development with Python.
- · Testing and handling of embedded systems.



# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor's degree in Telecommunication Engineering: Electronics**

Universidad de Sevilla, Spain (2016 - 2021)

ISTQB® Certified Tester Foundation Level

**Python Advanced Level Certification** 



### **LANGUAGES**

- · Spanish (Native)
- English (Fluent, C1)
- · Italian (Basic)